looniepolitics.com 2018-03-19

# Privacy Policy - Loonie Politics

Loonie Politics recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of visitors to our website.

Loonie Politics collects anonymous information about how visitors use our website. We log all web traffic and associate it with the visitor’s IP address. Our primary goal for tracking this data is to improve the reliability of our website, and improve the information we provide. We do not share this information with third parties.

When completing a survey, requesting information, or submitting a form you may be asked to provide personally identifying information, such as your name or e-mail address. This information will only be used to fulfill the specific request and will not be shared with third parties unless clearly indicated.

Some sections of our website may depend on the use of cookies to function properly. Cookies are used to make it possible for us to provide these services. We do not share this information with third parties unless clearly indicated.

We do not allow third parties to use cookies to track the pages that you visit on our website.

Loonie Politics makes no guarantees as to the Privacy Policies of pages that we link to.

If you have questions or concerns with any aspect of the privacy of your visit to our website, please feel free to contact us at [info@looniepolitics.com](mailto:info@looniepolitics.com).

If you decide to visit Loonie Politics website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. You agree to obtain changes to this Privacy Policy electronically by visiting this site. We require you to check back from time to time to review changes to our Privacy Policy.
